Kaephas Kain

Federal Way, WA - 253-315-1666 - kkain@mail.greenriver.edu

Software Development

I've begun my Junior year and will be increasing my knowledge of Object-Oriented Programming, specifically Java. We will be working in teams using Agile methods as well, and I look forward to learning how to work efficiently while collaborating. In my current job, I have experience working with clients and other employees to solve numerous IT and miscellaneous problems and working with other IT professionals to troubleshoot network and PC-related issues in a retail environment. I have a strong general understanding of PC hardware and software.

Skills

- Java Programming
- Basic Web Design (HTML/CSS/Javascript)
- Exposure to Python, SQL, PHP
- Knowledge of Excel & Word

- Intermediate Spanish
- A+ Certification
- Interpersonal communication
- Working knowledge of Quickbooks

Education

Green River College

Associate of Applied Science, 3/2017 Information Technology – Systems and Security Cumulative: 3.33 GPA; Major: 3.8 GPA

Bachelor of Applied Science, expected 6/2020 Information Technology – Software Development 3.92 GPA

Professional experience

Marlene's Market & Deli – Natural Foods and Supplements Store, Delicatessen

Store Supervisor, 4/2002 – 8/2009

Market Manager, 8/2009 – 11/2011

Supervise 60 plus employees in various tasks.

- Hire and dismiss employees and manage job schedules.
- Add and manage Web content.
- Pay bills and sign checks.

Accounts receivable/payable, 3/2008 – present

IT Coordinator 6/2010 – present.

- Coordinate with IT companies to manage our internal computer networks.
- Build PCs for the company.
- General computer maintenance.

Auburn Family Sports Center – Batting Cages, Fun Center for Kids, Birthday Parties

Supervisor, 9/1998-7/2001

- Repair broken equipment.
- Supervise 5-10 employees working birthday parties for customers' children and the Arcade.
- Defuse situations with customers and employees.